Contact

nursetiffanyj@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tiffany-jakubowski (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

IV Certified

Basic ECG

Therapeutic Communication

Certifications

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

BLS

ACLS

Certified Orthopaedic Nurse (ONC)

Honors-Awards

Daisy Nursing Award- Nominated Sharon Rominger Excellence in Nursing Award

Patient Education Award

DAISY Team Award

DAISY Nursing Award- Nominated

Publications

Multiple articles on gluten-free food

Saunders 2014-2015 Strategies for Test Success; Passing Nursing School and the NCLEX Exam, 3rd Edition

Multiple articles on dining-out glutenfree

Mosby's Textbook for the Home Care Aide, 3rd Edition

Multiple articles on dining-out glutenfree and living with celiac disease

Tiffany Jakubowski

BSN, RN, CMSRN, ONC

Longmont, Colorado

Summary

Registered Nurse with a passion for nurse education, process improvement, quality projects, evidence-based practice, and shared governance, currently pursuing a Doctorate of Nursing Practice as a Clinical Nurse Specialist (AGCNS) through the University of Colorado, Anschutz Medical Campus.

Personal interests include the 1940-1950's ball, vintage style, SCUBA diving, training for and running RunDisney half-marathon races, training and playing with my Border Collie/German Shepard mix, Star Trek fan, going to Denver Center for the Performing Arts shows/musicals, and traveling.

Experience

Longmont United Hospital RN, Clinical Nurse III, Clinical Scholar April 2014 - Present (6 years 3 months)

Longmont, Colorado

Primarily orthopedic care, including total joint replacement, fracture care, post-operative care, critical assessment, and pain management. Wound care "mini expert" (unit wound care resource person), Nurse Grand Rounds case research and presenter (2016), Hospital Emergency Response Team (2014-2016), charge nurse, preceptor, float nurse oriented to telemetry, oncology, and general med/surg.

Clinical Scholar- Trained through the Colorado Center for Nursing Excellence (CCNE) as a Clinical Scholar in 2018. Scholar for University of Northern Colorado and Regis University nursing students.

Multiple DAISY award nominations and nursing awards.

Vice President of the Professional Nursing Council 2018-2019. President of the Professional Nursing Council (re-titled Professional Practice Council) 2019-present. Poster presenter at the Professional Nursing Assembly in 2016, 2017, 2018, and 2019.

Member of the Patient Education, Meds Management, Leadership, Professional Development, and Planetree committees.

Alaris infusion pump super user for rollout and ongoing use.

High Reliability Organization (HRO) training team member.

UCHealth

RN

June 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Longmont, Colorado, United States

PRN Medical/Surgical RN on an acute care Medical/Surgical/Ortho/Tele floor.

Front Range Community College
Online Adjunct Instructor
January 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Online Instructor for HPR courses (Medical Terminology)

Front Range Community College Clinical/Adjunct Instructor-Nursing October 2013 - June 2016 (2 years 9 months) Longmont, Colorado

Secondary instructor for lab activities, including hands-on demonstration of nursing skills and skills check-off testing. Clinical instruction of PN and ADN students at various clinical facilities.

Cheyenne Regional Medical Center RN, Ortho/Neuro Floor July 2013 - April 2014 (10 months) Cheyenne, Wyoming

Ortho/Neuro/Trauma unit, charge nurse, preceptor, and member of the Ortho/ Neuro Unit Practice Council during the hospital's review and revision of the TPN policy.

American Heart Association NIH Stroke Scale Certification.

TNCC (Trauma Nurse Core Class)

Daisy Nursing Award nominee.

Longmont Clinic RN, Gastroenterology July 2012 - July 2013 (1 year 1 month)

Longmont, CO

Telephone triage, medication refills, procedure billing, patient education, pathology and patient communication, documentation of patient education and communication, medication administration

Lovely Lady Products
RN-Consultant/Guest Speaker
April 2013 - June 2013 (3 months)

Guest speaker, Celiac education, customer education, and educational material design.

Mollen Immunization Clinics

LPN-Injections

August 2010 - December 2012 (2 years 5 months)

Seasonal vaccination clinics including influenza vaccinations.

Front Range Community College

1 year 10 months

Nurse Aide Instructor

August 2010 - May 2012 (1 year 10 months)

Student instruction of nurse aide skills, rational for patient care, clinical observation of students, preparation for the state of Colorado CNA written and skills exam.

Nursing Tutor

August 2010 - May 2012 (1 year 10 months)

Boulder County Campus

Assisted students in finding specific learning obstacles and identifying goals for tutoring. Encouraging students through various teaching strategies, including visual, auditory, and hands-on learning, and explaining testing strategies.

Frasier Meadows Health Care Center

LPN

February 2010 - March 2011 (1 year 2 months)

Medication administration, injection administration, IV infusion administration, resident assessment, planning and implementation, resident education, straight-cath specimen collection, wound dressing changes, blood glucose checks, neurological checks, Med-A charting, tube feedings, breathing treatments, various resident cares.

Longmont United Hospital
Unit Coordinator/CNA
December 2008 - September 2010 (1 year 10 months)

Patient care, assistance with ADL's, lab sample and specimen collection, chart/graph vital signs, blood glucose testing, order entry, pediatric-specific training, cross-training as Unit Secretary.

Education

University of Colorado

Doctorate of Nursing Practice, Clinical Nurse Specialist

AGCNS · (2018 - 2022)

University of Northern Colorado

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2012 - 2013)

Front Range Community College LPN-RN, Nursing · (2011 - 2012)

Front Range Community College LPN, Licensed Practical Nurse · (2009 - 2009)

Front Range Community College CNA, Nurses Aide · (2008 - 2008)